// eslint-disable-next-line import/no-anonymous-default-export
export default[
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503a2",
    correctAnswer: "Harvard",
    options: [
      "Harvard",
      "Yale",
      "Cornell",
      "Princeton"
    ],
    question: "Which University, founded in 1636, is the oldest in the USA?",
    tags: [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503ee",
    correctAnswer: "De Militarized Zone",
    options: [
      "De Militarized Zone",
      "Definite Multivariate Zone",
      "Deregulated Monetary Zone",
      "Decompression Minimum Zone"
    ],
    question: "What does 'DMZ' stand for?",
    tags: [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "6355b7eee8b368eed3a68238",
    correctAnswer: "The g in 'green'",
    options: [
      "The g in 'green'",
      "The v in 'village'",
      "The r in 'red'",
      "The m in 'mother'"
    ],
    question: "In phonetics, which of these is an example of a plosive sound?",
    tags: [
      "language",
      "linguistics",
      "general_knowledge",
      "science"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc6a",
    correctAnswer: "Nudiustertian",
    options: [
      "Nudiustertian",
      "Poppycock",
      "Widdershins",
      "Erinaceous"
    ],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'the day before yesterday'?",
    tags: [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503f9",
    correctAnswer: "Robots",
    options: [
      "Robots",
      "Aliens",
      "Gods",
      "Wizards"
    ],
    question: "Transformers are ___________ in disguise. ",
    tags: [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62602e694b176d54800e3cd9",
    correctAnswer: "Riga",
    options: [
      "Riga",
      "Oslo",
      "Prague",
      "Rome"
    ],
    question: "Which of these cities is in Latvia?",
    tags: [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "geography"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62602d214b176d54800e3c81",
    correctAnswer: "Austria",
    options: [
      "Austria",
      "Bulgaria",
      "Sweden",
      "Ireland"
    ],
    question: "Where would you find the city of Vienna?",
    tags: [
      "cities",
      "europe",
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "6233874b0161109f922aac16",
    correctAnswer: "Yemen",
    options: [
      "Yemen",
      "Kuwait",
      "Qatar",
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ],
    question: "Which country at the southern tip of the Arabian Peninsula was previously known as Aden?",
    tags: [
      "geography"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd58",
    correctAnswer: "Russia",
    options: [
      "Russia",
      "China",
      "The USA",
      "Australia"
    ],
    question: "Which country has the largest amount of timezones on its mainland?",
    tags: [
      "general_knowledge",
      "geography"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "623742a7cb85f7ce9e949de3",
    correctAnswer: "Trinidad and Tobago",
    options: [
      "Trinidad and Tobago",
      "Dominican Republic",
      "Ecuador",
      "Malta"
    ],
    question: "Port of Spain is the capital city of which country?",
    tags: [
      "geography"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62399f24af96521963a0871e",
    correctAnswer: "Uruguay",
    options: [
      "Uruguay",
      "Brazil",
      "West Germany",
      "Argentina"
    ],
    question: "Which country won the 1950 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Brazil?",
    tags: [
      "sport"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950058",
    correctAnswer: "Bantamweight",
    options: [
      "Bantamweight",
      "Heavyweight",
      "Lightweight",
      "Subweight"
    ],
    question: "Which weight division in boxing lies between flyweight and featherweight?",
    tags: [
      "boxing",
      "words",
      "sport"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f89d",
    correctAnswer: "Cricket",
    options: [
      "Cricket",
      "Volleyball",
      "Badminton",
      "Ice Hockey"
    ],
    question: "With which sport is Shane Warne associated?",
    tags: [
      "people",
      "sport"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "easy",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950041",
    correctAnswer: "Oliver McCall",
    options: [
      "Oliver McCall",
      "Mike Tyson",
      "Frank Bruno",
      "Alex Brush"
    ],
    question: "Who was the first boxer to defeat Lennox Lewis in a professional bout?",
    tags: [
      "boxing",
      "firsts",
      "sport"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "hard",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500c1",
    correctAnswer: "Five",
    options: [
      "Five",
      "Six",
      "Seven",
      "Eight"
    ],
    question: "How Many Players Are In A Basketball Team?",
    tags: [
      "sport"
    ],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    difficulty: "medium",
    regions: [],
    isNiche: false
  }
]